<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Libertyville Real Estate Video Blog with Jan Leasure</title>
    <description>Our mission at Diamond Residential Mortgage is to be your best resource for Libertyville real estate advice. Whether you are a buyer, seller, or investor, our team of professionals can answer any questions you might have about real estate. If you are looking to buy or sell a home, you can get all the information and the latest updates, tips, and tricks from The Diamond Residential Mortgage, your professional Libertyville Real Estate Agents.</description>
    <link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2019 13:44:23 -0500</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2019 13:44:23 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.7.4</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>My #WineAboutLife Interview With Nik Champion</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/u_YZyRqjZLE?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I recently got a chance to drink some wine and share my backstory on the very first episode of “#WineAboutLife.” I hope you enjoy!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On my recent appearance on “#WineAboutLife,” I got to talk with host
Nik Champion about the experiences I’ve had that made me who I
am today. Nik Champion is the owner of Champion Allstate in Warrenville, IL.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Nik can be reached at 630-332-2555 or via email at
championagency@allstate.com&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For your convenience, I’ve provided timestamps of the interview
so you can jump ahead at your leisure:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;0:54—Two important events that shaped my mantra on life
2:47—How I apply this mindset to my business
3:47—The best advice I could ever give to anyone
5:02—The most emotionally gratifying mortgage transaction
I’ve ever participated in&lt;br /&gt;
7:19—How I got my nickname: “The Lake County Loan Goddess”
8:39—Other niche services I offer, including being a CLDP
Nik is always looking for more businesspeople and community
leaders to sit down for a future episode of “#WineAboutLife,” so
if you’re interested in being interviewed, go ahead and reach out
to him!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As always, if you have any questions for me or there’s anything I can help
you with, don’t hesitate to call or email me. I’d love to help you.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2019 16:57:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/my-wineaboutlife-interview-with-nik.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/my-wineaboutlife-interview-with-nik.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Self Defense Training for Realtors</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/DAy7TCO0wDM?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How many of you watching this knew that I was a Realtor?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There were a number of times that I was showing a home or sitting an open house and I was extremely uncomfortable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fortunately for me, there was never a disaster, but looking back after watching the Beverly Carter story about an agent who was tortured and killed during a showing and reading local headlines I felt that it was important to provide some sort of training to help keep our Lake County agents safe.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I recently attended a self defense class sponsored by two police officers, Anne and Kevin at Crossfit Freedom in Libertyville and decided that this is exactly the type of  skill that our agents need to be prepared for any situation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am sponsoring a Realtor Safety &amp;amp; Self Defense party and Luncheon on February 7th from 11am – 1pm, cohosted by Real Estate Attorney, Shameen Thakrar. Come dressed to play, be hungry, lunch will be provided by Real Clean Paleo our favorite healthy food!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Go home with skills and swag.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The regular price is $45 per person, but my sponsorship will cover $25 of that so your cost for the class and lunch is $20! You can RSVP at the Empower Self-Defense Facebook page or on my business page, Jan Leasure Diamond Residential Mortgage.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let’s make 2019 Safe and Prosperous!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jan 2019 14:44:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/self-defense-training-for-realtors.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/self-defense-training-for-realtors.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Wishing you a happy Thanksgiving</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/bHtlGQeyZlI?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Friends,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The 2018 holiday season has officially begun! We hope you are as excited
as we are.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We’d like to take a moment to express our gratitude to all of you this
Thanksgiving. We have met some truly wonderful people, and we’re
proud to have helped so many reach their real estate goals over the years.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We wouldn’t be where we are today without all of your support.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Enjoy your Thanksgiving dinner with all of your family and friends—
that’s what we plan to do!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the meantime, please don’t hesitate to reach out to us if you have
any real estate questions. We would be happy to help you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Happy Thanksgiving,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jan Leasure
Division President
Diamond Residential Mortgage
NMLS #213431
533 N. Milwaukee Avenue
Libertyville, IL 60048
Phone (847) 362-1335&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;jan.leasure@thedrmc.com&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2018 16:11:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/wishing-you-happy-thanksgiving.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/wishing-you-happy-thanksgiving.html</guid>
        
        <category>Diamond Residential Mortgage</category>
        
        <category>Home Decline</category>
        
        <category>Increasing Your Credit Score</category>
        
        <category>Foreclosure</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How Mortgage Rates Are Affecting the Market</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/_5tC333WIq8?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The average mortgage rate is at a seven-year high. Is this what’s behind the shift we’re seeing in the market?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The 30-year fixed mortgage rate currently stands at around 4.77%. That’s near a seven-year high, and almost 1% higher than just a year ago. This is the result of a steady rise starting last September and ending this May.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What impact is this having on the real estate market? It’s certainly true that affordability is down. In fact, one estimate from June found that home affordability is at a 10-year low. This is translating into fewer home sales, fewer viewings, and fewer mortgage applications.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, I don’t believe that the shifts in the mortgage rate is the primary mover of the changes we’re seeing in the real estate market. In fact, even at its current level, the mortgage rate is still historically low.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Instead, the big reason for the changes in the real estate market is the ongoing growth in prices. Over the past several years, home prices have gone up at close to twice the rate of inflation, and have far outstripped the growth of incomes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The price increases, in turn, have been caused by a lack of inventory, which has been shrinking for the past three years. In my opinion, it’s this lack of inventory (and the resulting hike in prices) that explains most of the effects on the real estate market that I listed above.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’re looking to sell, you should still have no trouble doing so. Demand continues to outstrip supply, and even with dropping affordability, it’s very likely that you would find a buyer quickly and at a top price.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’re looking to buy, the picture is more complex, because it’s so hard to predict what the mortgage rate might do in the near term. One thing we do know is that the severe lack of inventory is unlikely to change any time soon.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As always, if you have questions about the (area) real estate market, whether you’re buying or selling, you can give me a call or send me an email. I’m here to help.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 06 Nov 2018 17:14:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/how-mortgage-rates-are-affecting-market.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/how-mortgage-rates-are-affecting-market.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Dont Let a Big Down Payment Stop You From Owning Your Dream Home</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/HW0bo4e7OiU?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do you want to buy a house, but aren’t sure you can cover the down payment? Let’s talk about
some down-payment assistance programs that may be able to help.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Down payment assistance can be the difference between saying “yes”
or “no” to a first home. If you are interested in buying a home but don’t
have cash on hand for a down payment, or if you have a son, daughter
or any other friend or family member who would like to purchase a home
but doesn’t have cash for a down payment in the state of Illinois, there
are  several government programs that can assist you in securing a
down payment for your new dream home.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The First Home Illinois Program This program offers a forgivable
loan of $7,500 to buyers who will live in their new home for at least 5
years. This program will discontinue in December 2018, so to take
advantage of this down-payment assistance opportunity, your home
loan must be originated by December 15, 2018.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Even though this program will be discontinued for much of Illinois past
2018, there are other down-payment assistance programs that will be
available moving forward into 2019 and beyond:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;A forgivable loan of up to $6,000, with the amount based on the total
price of the home, forgivable after 5 years.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;A $7,500 deferred program. This loan is repaid through a second
mortgage the buyer doesn’t make payments on, but is reimbursed when
you sell your home.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;A $10,000 no-interest loan repaid through a monthly payment of
$83 for 120 months.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’d like to find out more about these programs, check out this flier!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have anything other questions regarding down-payment
assistance in the purchase of your new home, please feel free to
give me a call or send me an email today. I’d love to hear from you.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 05 Sep 2018 10:36:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/dont-let-big-down-payment-stop-you-from.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/dont-let-big-down-payment-stop-you-from.html</guid>
        
        <category>Libertyville Restaurants</category>
        
        <category>Libertyville Real Estate Other</category>
        
        <category>Increasing Your Credit Score</category>
        
        <category>Homebuyer Tips</category>
        
        <category>Life Lessons</category>
        
        <category>The Mortgage Minute</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>What Does Reduced Home Affordability Mean for You?</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/PHFogn3Kjuc?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Home affordability is shrinking fast. Here’s what you should do to get ahead of the curve.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Home affordability is shrinking rapidly, according to research by Arch Mortgage Insurance. In the first quarter, affordability (defined as the size of the monthly mortgage payment needed to buy a home) dropped by 5%. This was mainly due to the increase in mortgage rates. As a consequence, more people are now stretched and taking on greater debt relative to their income. Other buyers are being pushed out of the market altogether.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That’s not all. Affordability is expected to drop an additional 15% to 20% by the end of the year. That’s because home prices continue to rise, and the Federal Reserve is expected to ratchet up its reference interest rate, which often leads mortgage rates, three more times this year.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What does this mean for you?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’re looking to sell, you won’t have a hard time finding a buyer. Even with decreasing affordability, demand for homes still far outstrips supply. That means that this spring and summer might see an additional rush on the real estate market. It also means that right now might be a very good time to list your home if you’ve been thinking about selling for a while.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;THERE’S NO NEED TO PANIC IF YOU’RE A HOMEBUYER.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On the other hand, if you are thinking of buying a home, you might think that this news spells doom for you. However, there’s no need to panic. While affordability is dropping, it is still well above historic averages (just like current mortgage rates). In fact, Arch Mortgage Insurance estimates that homes are now 15% to 20% more affordable than they have been in the period from 1987 to 2004. When rates go up, it will affect what your monthly payments will be on a new home. From this perspective, it makes sense to move now in case you’ve been looking to buy before rates rise further.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So what’s the next step? If you’re thinking about buying or selling a home, give us a call. We’d be happy to answer any questions you may have. We look forward to hearing from you soon.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jun 2018 14:45:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/home-affordability-is-shrinking-fast.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/home-affordability-is-shrinking-fast.html</guid>
        
        <category>Diamond Residential Mortgage</category>
        
        <category>Libertyville Restaurants</category>
        
        <category>Libertyville Real Estate Other</category>
        
        <category>Libertyville Mortgages</category>
        
        <category>Home Decline</category>
        
        <category>Real Estate Market Update</category>
        
        <category>Foreclosure</category>
        
        <category>The Mortgage Minute</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Starter and Trade-Up Homes are in High Demand</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/uk62-datsQg?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The real estate market remains red-hot. In fact, Zillow estimates that homes sold more quickly in 2017 than ever before. And 2018 seems on-pace to beat 2017. However, one segment of the real estate market seems to be lagging.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m talking about luxury homes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Prices in the top 5% of the real estate market increased just 5.1% in 2017, almost 2% lower than the rest of the market. What’s going on?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Affordability does not seem to be an issue: more Americans can afford a top-level home than ever before. Instead, it might come down to two other factors.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=DEMAND AND SUPPLY ARE MORE EVENLY MATCHED AT THE TOP OF THE MARKET.%20http://localhost:4000/starter-and-trade-up-homes-are-in-high.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“DEMAND AND SUPPLY ARE MORE EVENLY MATCHED AT THE TOP OF THE MARKET.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First, uncertainty surrounding the new tax bill could be affecting luxury homes more strongly, and this might be the reason why some potential buyers are choosing to sit and wait until the details of the tax plan become more clear. Second, there is simply a greater supply of luxury homes compared to other types of homes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In other words, demand and supply are more evenly matched at the top of the market, while in other segments, demand far outstrips supply.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’ve been thinking about trading up to a luxury home, now might be the perfect time to do so. The red-hot demand for starter and trade-up homes means you could sell your home for top dollar and at record speed. The limited price growth and greater inventory at the luxury end means you could have your pick, and find a special, unique, and customized home that perfectly suits your preferences.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any questions about the current Central Illinois real estate market, don’t hesitate to give me a call or send me an email. I look forward to hearing from you soon.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 16 May 2018 13:28:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/starter-and-trade-up-homes-are-in-high.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/starter-and-trade-up-homes-are-in-high.html</guid>
        
        <category>Homebuyer Tips</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>3 Questions to Ask an Agent Before Hiring Them</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/eOEDwWrvc_w?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Before hiring a real estate agent, you need to do some vetting. Here are the questions that we recommend you ask.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Buying or selling a home is a major project. Having a trustworthy agent to guide you through that project can be an invaluable asset. But how can you vet potential real estate agents to see who would be a good fit for you? Here are three important questions you should ask to get started:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1. “How many homes have you sold in the last 12 months?”&lt;/strong&gt; Many real estate agents will tell you the number of years they have in the business. That’s useful, but their recent activity can be more relevant than their total experience. Asking this question can tell you how well they know the market, as well as how successful you can expect them to be in your case.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bonus Question: You will probably want to ask whether the agent works primarily with buyers or sellers, because many agents specialize to some extent in one or the other.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2. “Can I have the contact info for your last three deals?”&lt;/strong&gt; Anybody can say they are a marvelously effective real estate agent. But talking to actual past clients can help you decide whether this is true or a bunch of hot air. When you do talk to a real estate agent’s previous clients, you don’t need to get too fancy to get useful information. Simply ask them to share their experience.
 YOU WANT TO GET A SENSE THAT THIS AGENT IS SOMEBODY YOU CAN TRUST.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3. “What is your strategy for my specific needs?”&lt;/strong&gt; As a buyer, you will want the agent to explain how they will search for your new home, how many homes you can expect to see, and how the agent handles multiple offers. As a seller, you will want to know how and where the agent will advertise your home.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So what kinds of answers should you look for to these questions?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ideally, you will want to get a sense that this agent is somebody you can trust and that you feel comfortable working with.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At the same time, you will want them to be experienced and diligent, as evidenced by recent successful deals and a concrete plan of action for your situation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you ever want to know how I measure up on these questions, you can always give me a call at (847) 362-1335. I’d love to hear what your specific situation is and whether I would be a good match to help you in the current Libertyville real estate market.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 10:05:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/3-questions-to-ask-agent-before-hiring.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/3-questions-to-ask-agent-before-hiring.html</guid>
        
        <category>Libertyville Real Estate Other</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How to Get Pre-Approved for a Mortgage</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/Io_qVPjqu1Y?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’re buying a home with a mortgage, you absolutely need to get a pre-approval first. Here’s why.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There’s no doubt about it. It’s a very competitive market today if you are looking to buy a home.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Inventory is near record lows, and more and more homebuyers are entering the market. This means you need every advantage to grab that perfect home when you do find it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One no-brainer is to get pre-approved for a mortgage. A pre-approval informs you of how much you can borrow and it’s something you will need to do at a later point anyway.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A pre-approval can mean the difference between having your offer accepted or having to watch your dream home go to somebody else in a crazy market like this.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In spite of all these good reasons, less than 10% of buyers who got a mortgage get pre-approved by the lender who originated the loan. In other words, you can definitely get a leg up on the competition by starting your home search at the loan office rather than at the open house.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=A PRE-APPROVAL DEFINITELY GIVES YOU A LEG UP ON THE COMPETITION.%20http://localhost:4000/how-to-get-pre-approved-for-mortgage.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“A PRE-APPROVAL DEFINITELY GIVES YOU A LEG UP ON THE COMPETITION.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here are a few things that you will need:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1. Proof of income.&lt;/strong&gt; At a minimum, lenders will want to see pay stubs from the past 30 days showing your year-to-date income, two years of federal tax returns, and two years of W2 forms from your employer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2. Proof of assets.&lt;/strong&gt; You will need to present statements from your checking, savings, or investment accounts to prove that you have funds for the down payment and closing costs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3. Good credit.&lt;/strong&gt; Most lenders reserve the best rates for homebuyers with a credit score of 740 or above. You can still qualify for a mortgage with a lower credit score, but a good lender will also recommend ways that you can improve your credit and qualify for a better loan.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These are the biggest and most common things you will need to get pre-approved, though your lender might want to see some other documents as well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Once you are pre-approved, the buying process will be faster, more convenient, and less stressful. Most importantly, it will make it more likely that your offer for that perfect home gets accepted.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any questions for me or need any additional assistance, don’t hesitate to give me a call or send me an email. I look forward to hearing from you soon.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 03 Apr 2018 11:22:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/how-to-get-pre-approved-for-mortgage.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/how-to-get-pre-approved-for-mortgage.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>5 Ways to Invest in Real Estate</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/8TjUiPoavrU?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Real estate investing is on the rise. Here are five different ways you can get involved.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Investing in real estate is no longer restricted to the super wealthy. According to a recent survey, real estate investors now make up 15% of the population. That translates to almost 50 million individuals who invest in at least one property other than their primary residence.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In fact, 89% of U.S. investors are interested in putting their money in real estate because of benefits such as cash flow, tax incentives, leverage, and value appreciation that come with investing in multiple properties.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=REAL ESTATE INVESTING IS ON THE RISE. HERE ARE FIVE DIFFERENT WAYS YOU CAN GET INVOLVED.%20http://localhost:4000/5-ways-to-invest-in-real-estate.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“REAL ESTATE INVESTING IS ON THE RISE. HERE ARE FIVE DIFFERENT WAYS YOU CAN GET INVOLVED.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Are you curious about investing in real estate? If so, here are five different ways you can get started:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1. Buy and rent&lt;/strong&gt;
This is probably the most traditional way to invest in real estate. It simply involves buying a property and renting it out. Now is a good time for this kind of investing because rental rates are on the rise (8% since last year) but the downside of this investing approach is the time and effort needed to manage and maintain your investment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2. Buy and sell&lt;/strong&gt;
Also known as home flipping, this involves buying a property and reselling it soon after for a profit. Home flipping has offered a record-breaking 49% return in 2016.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3. Real estate investment groups&lt;/strong&gt;
Real estate investment groups are organizations that buy a set of properties and then sell them to individual investors.The main benefit of this approach is that you typically do not need to act as the landlord because the investment group handles property management for you (for a fee of course).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;4. Crowdfunding sites&lt;/strong&gt;
Recently, there’s been an explosion of sites such as Prosper and Lending Club, which allow individuals to invest in various real estate development projects. Through crowdfunding sites, you can be a part of a large-scale property investment while investing only a moderate amount of money. On the other hand, crowdfunding sites act as a middleman and charge fees which can eat into your profits.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;5. REITs&lt;/strong&gt;
Real estate investment trusts (REITs) are like mutual funds for real estate.They typically pay high dividends. However, they also do not offer all of the typical benefits of investing in real estate, such as increased leverage and tax benefits.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Each of these investing approaches offers a tradeoff between possible profits, risks, and costs. The one constant is that you can minimize your risks with due diligence and by consulting with an experienced real estate professional.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any questions for us or you’re interested in investing in real estate yourself, don’t hesitate to give me a call or send me an email. I look forward to hearing from you.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2017 14:43:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/5-ways-to-invest-in-real-estate.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/5-ways-to-invest-in-real-estate.html</guid>
        
        <category>Homebuyer Tips</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
