<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" xmlns:itunesu="http://www.itunesu.com/feed" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Libertyville Real Estate Podcast with Jan Leasure</title>
    <link>http://localhost:4000</link>
    <atom10:link xmlns:atom10="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="http://localhost:4000"/>
    <description>If you are looking to buy or sell a home, get all the information and the latest updates, tips, and tricks from Diamond Residential Mortgage - your professional Libertyville Real Estate Agents.</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <managingEditor>Jan Leasure</managingEditor>
    <lastBuildDate>2019-08-01 13:44:23 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <media:copyright>Jan Leasure</media:copyright>
    <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000/img/podcast.jpg"/>
    <media:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Libertyville, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</media:keywords>
    <media:category scheme="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd">Education</media:category>
    <itunes:owner>
      <itunes:email>jan.leasure@thedrmc.com</itunes:email>
      <itunes:name>Jan Leasure</itunes:name>
    </itunes:owner>
    <itunes:author>Jan Leasure</itunes:author>
    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
    <itunes:image href="http://localhost:4000/img/podcast.jpg"/>
    <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Libertyville, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
    <itunes:subtitle>Learn all the tips, tricks and more for buyers and sellers in the Libertyville Area Real Estate Market</itunes:subtitle>
    <itunes:summary>If you are looking to buy or sell a home, get all the information and the latest updates, tips, and tricks from Diamond Residential Mortgage - your professional Libertyville Real Estate Agents.</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:category text="Education"/>
    
      <item>
        <title>My #WineAboutLife Interview With Nik Champion</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/my-wineaboutlife-interview-with-nik.html</link>
        
        <author>Jan Leasure</author>
        <pubDate>2019-03-01 16:57:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <guid></guid>
        <description>

I recently got a chance to drink some wine and share my backstory on the very first episode of “#WineAboutLife.” I hope you enjoy!

On my recent appearance on “#WineAboutLife,” I got to talk with host
Nik Champion about the experiences I’ve had that made me who I
am today. Nik Champion is the owner of Champion Allstate in Warrenville, IL.

Nik can be reached at 630-332-2555 or via email at
championagency@allstate.com

For your convenience, I’ve provided timestamps of the interview
so you can jump ahead at your leisure:

0:54—Two important events that shaped my mantra on life
2:47—How I apply this mindset to my business
3:47—The best advice I could ever give to anyone
5:02—The most emotionally gratifying mortgage transaction
I’ve ever participated in
7:19—How I got my nickname: “The Lake County Loan Goddess”
8:39—Other niche services I offer, including being a CLDP
Nik is always looking for more businesspeople and community
leaders to sit down for a future episode of “#WineAboutLife,” so
if you’re interested in being interviewed, go ahead and reach out
to him!

As always, if you have any questions for me or there’s anything I can help
you with, don’t hesitate to call or email me. I’d love to help you.
</description>
        <enclosure url="" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>

I recently got a chance to drink some wine and share my backstory on the very first episode of “#WineAboutLife.” I hope you enjoy!

</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Jan Leasure</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>

I recently got a chance to drink some wine and share my backstory on the very first episode of “#WineAboutLife.” I hope you enjoy!

</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Libertyville, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Self Defense Training for Realtors</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/self-defense-training-for-realtors.html</link>
        
        <author>Jan Leasure</author>
        <pubDate>2019-01-31 14:44:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <guid></guid>
        <description>

How many of you watching this knew that I was a Realtor?

There were a number of times that I was showing a home or sitting an open house and I was extremely uncomfortable.

Fortunately for me, there was never a disaster, but looking back after watching the Beverly Carter story about an agent who was tortured and killed during a showing and reading local headlines I felt that it was important to provide some sort of training to help keep our Lake County agents safe.

I recently attended a self defense class sponsored by two police officers, Anne and Kevin at Crossfit Freedom in Libertyville and decided that this is exactly the type of  skill that our agents need to be prepared for any situation.

I am sponsoring a Realtor Safety &amp; Self Defense party and Luncheon on February 7th from 11am – 1pm, cohosted by Real Estate Attorney, Shameen Thakrar. Come dressed to play, be hungry, lunch will be provided by Real Clean Paleo our favorite healthy food!

Go home with skills and swag.

The regular price is $45 per person, but my sponsorship will cover $25 of that so your cost for the class and lunch is $20! You can RSVP at the Empower Self-Defense Facebook page or on my business page, Jan Leasure Diamond Residential Mortgage.

Let’s make 2019 Safe and Prosperous!
</description>
        <enclosure url="" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>

How many of you watching this knew that I was a Realtor?

</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Jan Leasure</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>

How many of you watching this knew that I was a Realtor?

</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Libertyville, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Wishing you a happy Thanksgiving</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/wishing-you-happy-thanksgiving.html</link>
        
          <category>Diamond Residential Mortgage</category>
        
          <category>Home Decline</category>
        
          <category>Increasing Your Credit Score</category>
        
          <category>Foreclosure</category>
        
        <author>Jan Leasure</author>
        <pubDate>2018-11-12 16:11:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <guid></guid>
        <description>

Friends,

The 2018 holiday season has officially begun! We hope you are as excited
as we are.

We’d like to take a moment to express our gratitude to all of you this
Thanksgiving. We have met some truly wonderful people, and we’re
proud to have helped so many reach their real estate goals over the years.

We wouldn’t be where we are today without all of your support.

Enjoy your Thanksgiving dinner with all of your family and friends—
that’s what we plan to do!

In the meantime, please don’t hesitate to reach out to us if you have
any real estate questions. We would be happy to help you.

Happy Thanksgiving,

Jan Leasure
Division President
Diamond Residential Mortgage
NMLS #213431
533 N. Milwaukee Avenue
Libertyville, IL 60048
Phone (847) 362-1335

jan.leasure@thedrmc.com
</description>
        <enclosure url="" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>

Friends,

</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Jan Leasure</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>

Friends,

</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Libertyville, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>How Mortgage Rates Are Affecting the Market</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/how-mortgage-rates-are-affecting-market.html</link>
        
        <author>Jan Leasure</author>
        <pubDate>2018-11-06 17:14:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <guid></guid>
        <description>

The average mortgage rate is at a seven-year high. Is this what’s behind the shift we’re seeing in the market?

The 30-year fixed mortgage rate currently stands at around 4.77%. That’s near a seven-year high, and almost 1% higher than just a year ago. This is the result of a steady rise starting last September and ending this May.

What impact is this having on the real estate market? It’s certainly true that affordability is down. In fact, one estimate from June found that home affordability is at a 10-year low. This is translating into fewer home sales, fewer viewings, and fewer mortgage applications.

However, I don’t believe that the shifts in the mortgage rate is the primary mover of the changes we’re seeing in the real estate market. In fact, even at its current level, the mortgage rate is still historically low.

Instead, the big reason for the changes in the real estate market is the ongoing growth in prices. Over the past several years, home prices have gone up at close to twice the rate of inflation, and have far outstripped the growth of incomes.

The price increases, in turn, have been caused by a lack of inventory, which has been shrinking for the past three years. In my opinion, it’s this lack of inventory (and the resulting hike in prices) that explains most of the effects on the real estate market that I listed above.

If you’re looking to sell, you should still have no trouble doing so. Demand continues to outstrip supply, and even with dropping affordability, it’s very likely that you would find a buyer quickly and at a top price.

If you’re looking to buy, the picture is more complex, because it’s so hard to predict what the mortgage rate might do in the near term. One thing we do know is that the severe lack of inventory is unlikely to change any time soon.

As always, if you have questions about the (area) real estate market, whether you’re buying or selling, you can give me a call or send me an email. I’m here to help.
</description>
        <enclosure url="" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>

The average mortgage rate is at a seven-year high. Is this what’s behind the shift we’re seeing in the market?

</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Jan Leasure</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>

The average mortgage rate is at a seven-year high. Is this what’s behind the shift we’re seeing in the market?

</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Libertyville, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Dont Let a Big Down Payment Stop You From Owning Your Dream Home</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/dont-let-big-down-payment-stop-you-from.html</link>
        
          <category>Libertyville Restaurants</category>
        
          <category>Libertyville Real Estate Other</category>
        
          <category>Increasing Your Credit Score</category>
        
          <category>Homebuyer Tips</category>
        
          <category>Life Lessons</category>
        
          <category>The Mortgage Minute</category>
        
        <author>Jan Leasure</author>
        <pubDate>2018-09-05 10:36:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid></guid>
        <description>

Do you want to buy a house, but aren’t sure you can cover the down payment? Let’s talk about
some down-payment assistance programs that may be able to help.

Down payment assistance can be the difference between saying “yes”
or “no” to a first home. If you are interested in buying a home but don’t
have cash on hand for a down payment, or if you have a son, daughter
or any other friend or family member who would like to purchase a home
but doesn’t have cash for a down payment in the state of Illinois, there
are  several government programs that can assist you in securing a
down payment for your new dream home.

The First Home Illinois Program This program offers a forgivable
loan of $7,500 to buyers who will live in their new home for at least 5
years. This program will discontinue in December 2018, so to take
advantage of this down-payment assistance opportunity, your home
loan must be originated by December 15, 2018.

Even though this program will be discontinued for much of Illinois past
2018, there are other down-payment assistance programs that will be
available moving forward into 2019 and beyond:


  
    A forgivable loan of up to $6,000, with the amount based on the total
price of the home, forgivable after 5 years.
  
  
    A $7,500 deferred program. This loan is repaid through a second
mortgage the buyer doesn’t make payments on, but is reimbursed when
you sell your home.
  
  
    A $10,000 no-interest loan repaid through a monthly payment of
$83 for 120 months.
  


If you’d like to find out more about these programs, check out this flier!

If you have anything other questions regarding down-payment
assistance in the purchase of your new home, please feel free to
give me a call or send me an email today. I’d love to hear from you.
</description>
        <enclosure url="" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>

Do you want to buy a house, but aren’t sure you can cover the down payment? Let’s talk about
some down-payment assistance programs that may be able to help.

</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Jan Leasure</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>

Do you want to buy a house, but aren’t sure you can cover the down payment? Let’s talk about
some down-payment assistance programs that may be able to help.

</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Libertyville, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>What Does Reduced Home Affordability Mean for You?</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/home-affordability-is-shrinking-fast.html</link>
        
          <category>Diamond Residential Mortgage</category>
        
          <category>Libertyville Restaurants</category>
        
          <category>Libertyville Real Estate Other</category>
        
          <category>Libertyville Mortgages</category>
        
          <category>Home Decline</category>
        
          <category>Real Estate Market Update</category>
        
          <category>Foreclosure</category>
        
          <category>The Mortgage Minute</category>
        
        <author>Jan Leasure</author>
        <pubDate>2018-06-15 14:45:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Jan+Leasure/Libertyville+Mortgage-+What+Does+Reduced+Home+Affordability+Mean+for+You%253F.mp4</guid>
        <description>

Home affordability is shrinking fast. Here’s what you should do to get ahead of the curve.

Home affordability is shrinking rapidly, according to research by Arch Mortgage Insurance. In the first quarter, affordability (defined as the size of the monthly mortgage payment needed to buy a home) dropped by 5%. This was mainly due to the increase in mortgage rates. As a consequence, more people are now stretched and taking on greater debt relative to their income. Other buyers are being pushed out of the market altogether.

That’s not all. Affordability is expected to drop an additional 15% to 20% by the end of the year. That’s because home prices continue to rise, and the Federal Reserve is expected to ratchet up its reference interest rate, which often leads mortgage rates, three more times this year.

What does this mean for you?

If you’re looking to sell, you won’t have a hard time finding a buyer. Even with decreasing affordability, demand for homes still far outstrips supply. That means that this spring and summer might see an additional rush on the real estate market. It also means that right now might be a very good time to list your home if you’ve been thinking about selling for a while.

THERE’S NO NEED TO PANIC IF YOU’RE A HOMEBUYER.

On the other hand, if you are thinking of buying a home, you might think that this news spells doom for you. However, there’s no need to panic. While affordability is dropping, it is still well above historic averages (just like current mortgage rates). In fact, Arch Mortgage Insurance estimates that homes are now 15% to 20% more affordable than they have been in the period from 1987 to 2004. When rates go up, it will affect what your monthly payments will be on a new home. From this perspective, it makes sense to move now in case you’ve been looking to buy before rates rise further.

So what’s the next step? If you’re thinking about buying or selling a home, give us a call. We’d be happy to answer any questions you may have. We look forward to hearing from you soon.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Jan+Leasure/Libertyville+Mortgage-+What+Does+Reduced+Home+Affordability+Mean+for+You%253F.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Jan+Leasure/Libertyville+Mortgage-+What+Does+Reduced+Home+Affordability+Mean+for+You%253F.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>

Home affordability is shrinking fast. Here’s what you should do to get ahead of the curve.

</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Jan Leasure</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>

Home affordability is shrinking fast. Here’s what you should do to get ahead of the curve.

</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Libertyville, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Starter and Trade-Up Homes are in High Demand</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/starter-and-trade-up-homes-are-in-high.html</link>
        
          <category>Homebuyer Tips</category>
        
        <author>Jan Leasure</author>
        <pubDate>2018-05-16 13:28:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Jan+Leasure/Libertyville+Mortgage-+Starter+and+Trade-Up+Homes+are+in+High+Demand.mp4</guid>
        <description>

The real estate market remains red-hot. In fact, Zillow estimates that homes sold more quickly in 2017 than ever before. And 2018 seems on-pace to beat 2017. However, one segment of the real estate market seems to be lagging.

I’m talking about luxury homes.

Prices in the top 5% of the real estate market increased just 5.1% in 2017, almost 2% lower than the rest of the market. What’s going on?

Affordability does not seem to be an issue: more Americans can afford a top-level home than ever before. Instead, it might come down to two other factors.

“DEMAND AND SUPPLY ARE MORE EVENLY MATCHED AT THE TOP OF THE MARKET.”

First, uncertainty surrounding the new tax bill could be affecting luxury homes more strongly, and this might be the reason why some potential buyers are choosing to sit and wait until the details of the tax plan become more clear. Second, there is simply a greater supply of luxury homes compared to other types of homes.

In other words, demand and supply are more evenly matched at the top of the market, while in other segments, demand far outstrips supply.

If you’ve been thinking about trading up to a luxury home, now might be the perfect time to do so. The red-hot demand for starter and trade-up homes means you could sell your home for top dollar and at record speed. The limited price growth and greater inventory at the luxury end means you could have your pick, and find a special, unique, and customized home that perfectly suits your preferences.

If you have any questions about the current Central Illinois real estate market, don’t hesitate to give me a call or send me an email. I look forward to hearing from you soon.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Jan+Leasure/Libertyville+Mortgage-+Starter+and+Trade-Up+Homes+are+in+High+Demand.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Jan+Leasure/Libertyville+Mortgage-+Starter+and+Trade-Up+Homes+are+in+High+Demand.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>

The real estate market remains red-hot. In fact, Zillow estimates that homes sold more quickly in 2017 than ever before. And 2018 seems on-pace to beat 2017. However, one segment of the real estate market seems to be lagging.

</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Jan Leasure</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>

The real estate market remains red-hot. In fact, Zillow estimates that homes sold more quickly in 2017 than ever before. And 2018 seems on-pace to beat 2017. However, one segment of the real estate market seems to be lagging.

</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Libertyville, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>3 Questions to Ask an Agent Before Hiring Them</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/3-questions-to-ask-agent-before-hiring.html</link>
        
          <category>Libertyville Real Estate Other</category>
        
        <author>Jan Leasure</author>
        <pubDate>2018-04-26 10:05:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Jan+Leasure/Libertyville+Mortgage-+3+Questions+to+Ask+an+Agent+Before+Hiring+Them.mp4</guid>
        <description>

Before hiring a real estate agent, you need to do some vetting. Here are the questions that we recommend you ask.

Buying or selling a home is a major project. Having a trustworthy agent to guide you through that project can be an invaluable asset. But how can you vet potential real estate agents to see who would be a good fit for you? Here are three important questions you should ask to get started:

1. “How many homes have you sold in the last 12 months?” Many real estate agents will tell you the number of years they have in the business. That’s useful, but their recent activity can be more relevant than their total experience. Asking this question can tell you how well they know the market, as well as how successful you can expect them to be in your case.

Bonus Question: You will probably want to ask whether the agent works primarily with buyers or sellers, because many agents specialize to some extent in one or the other.

2. “Can I have the contact info for your last three deals?” Anybody can say they are a marvelously effective real estate agent. But talking to actual past clients can help you decide whether this is true or a bunch of hot air. When you do talk to a real estate agent’s previous clients, you don’t need to get too fancy to get useful information. Simply ask them to share their experience.
 YOU WANT TO GET A SENSE THAT THIS AGENT IS SOMEBODY YOU CAN TRUST.

3. “What is your strategy for my specific needs?” As a buyer, you will want the agent to explain how they will search for your new home, how many homes you can expect to see, and how the agent handles multiple offers. As a seller, you will want to know how and where the agent will advertise your home.

So what kinds of answers should you look for to these questions?

Ideally, you will want to get a sense that this agent is somebody you can trust and that you feel comfortable working with.

At the same time, you will want them to be experienced and diligent, as evidenced by recent successful deals and a concrete plan of action for your situation.

If you ever want to know how I measure up on these questions, you can always give me a call at (847) 362-1335. I’d love to hear what your specific situation is and whether I would be a good match to help you in the current Libertyville real estate market.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Jan+Leasure/Libertyville+Mortgage-+3+Questions+to+Ask+an+Agent+Before+Hiring+Them.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Jan+Leasure/Libertyville+Mortgage-+3+Questions+to+Ask+an+Agent+Before+Hiring+Them.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>

Before hiring a real estate agent, you need to do some vetting. Here are the questions that we recommend you ask.

</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Jan Leasure</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>

Before hiring a real estate agent, you need to do some vetting. Here are the questions that we recommend you ask.

</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Libertyville, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>How to Get Pre-Approved for a Mortgage</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/how-to-get-pre-approved-for-mortgage.html</link>
        
        <author>Jan Leasure</author>
        <pubDate>2018-04-03 11:22:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Jan+Leasure/Libertyville+Mortgage-+mortgage+approval.mp4</guid>
        <description>

If you’re buying a home with a mortgage, you absolutely need to get a pre-approval first. Here’s why.

There’s no doubt about it. It’s a very competitive market today if you are looking to buy a home.

Inventory is near record lows, and more and more homebuyers are entering the market. This means you need every advantage to grab that perfect home when you do find it.

One no-brainer is to get pre-approved for a mortgage. A pre-approval informs you of how much you can borrow and it’s something you will need to do at a later point anyway.

A pre-approval can mean the difference between having your offer accepted or having to watch your dream home go to somebody else in a crazy market like this.

In spite of all these good reasons, less than 10% of buyers who got a mortgage get pre-approved by the lender who originated the loan. In other words, you can definitely get a leg up on the competition by starting your home search at the loan office rather than at the open house.

“A PRE-APPROVAL DEFINITELY GIVES YOU A LEG UP ON THE COMPETITION.”

Here are a few things that you will need:

1. Proof of income. At a minimum, lenders will want to see pay stubs from the past 30 days showing your year-to-date income, two years of federal tax returns, and two years of W2 forms from your employer.

2. Proof of assets. You will need to present statements from your checking, savings, or investment accounts to prove that you have funds for the down payment and closing costs.

3. Good credit. Most lenders reserve the best rates for homebuyers with a credit score of 740 or above. You can still qualify for a mortgage with a lower credit score, but a good lender will also recommend ways that you can improve your credit and qualify for a better loan.

These are the biggest and most common things you will need to get pre-approved, though your lender might want to see some other documents as well.

Once you are pre-approved, the buying process will be faster, more convenient, and less stressful. Most importantly, it will make it more likely that your offer for that perfect home gets accepted.

If you have any questions for me or need any additional assistance, don’t hesitate to give me a call or send me an email. I look forward to hearing from you soon.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Jan+Leasure/Libertyville+Mortgage-+mortgage+approval.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Jan+Leasure/Libertyville+Mortgage-+mortgage+approval.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>

If you’re buying a home with a mortgage, you absolutely need to get a pre-approval first. Here’s why.

</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Jan Leasure</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>

If you’re buying a home with a mortgage, you absolutely need to get a pre-approval first. Here’s why.

</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Libertyville, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>5 Ways to Invest in Real Estate</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/5-ways-to-invest-in-real-estate.html</link>
        
          <category>Homebuyer Tips</category>
        
        <author>Jan Leasure</author>
        <pubDate>2017-09-15 14:43:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>http://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Jan%20Leasure/Libertyville%20Mortgage-%205%20Ways%20to%20Invest%20in%20Real%20Estate.mp4</guid>
        <description>

Real estate investing is on the rise. Here are five different ways you can get involved.

Investing in real estate is no longer restricted to the super wealthy. According to a recent survey, real estate investors now make up 15% of the population. That translates to almost 50 million individuals who invest in at least one property other than their primary residence.

In fact, 89% of U.S. investors are interested in putting their money in real estate because of benefits such as cash flow, tax incentives, leverage, and value appreciation that come with investing in multiple properties.

“REAL ESTATE INVESTING IS ON THE RISE. HERE ARE FIVE DIFFERENT WAYS YOU CAN GET INVOLVED.”

Are you curious about investing in real estate? If so, here are five different ways you can get started:

1. Buy and rent
This is probably the most traditional way to invest in real estate. It simply involves buying a property and renting it out. Now is a good time for this kind of investing because rental rates are on the rise (8% since last year) but the downside of this investing approach is the time and effort needed to manage and maintain your investment.

2. Buy and sell
Also known as home flipping, this involves buying a property and reselling it soon after for a profit. Home flipping has offered a record-breaking 49% return in 2016.

3. Real estate investment groups
Real estate investment groups are organizations that buy a set of properties and then sell them to individual investors.The main benefit of this approach is that you typically do not need to act as the landlord because the investment group handles property management for you (for a fee of course).

4. Crowdfunding sites
Recently, there’s been an explosion of sites such as Prosper and Lending Club, which allow individuals to invest in various real estate development projects. Through crowdfunding sites, you can be a part of a large-scale property investment while investing only a moderate amount of money. On the other hand, crowdfunding sites act as a middleman and charge fees which can eat into your profits.

5. REITs
Real estate investment trusts (REITs) are like mutual funds for real estate.They typically pay high dividends. However, they also do not offer all of the typical benefits of investing in real estate, such as increased leverage and tax benefits.

Each of these investing approaches offers a tradeoff between possible profits, risks, and costs. The one constant is that you can minimize your risks with due diligence and by consulting with an experienced real estate professional.

If you have any questions for us or you’re interested in investing in real estate yourself, don’t hesitate to give me a call or send me an email. I look forward to hearing from you.
</description>
        <enclosure url="http://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Jan%20Leasure/Libertyville%20Mortgage-%205%20Ways%20to%20Invest%20in%20Real%20Estate.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="http://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Jan%20Leasure/Libertyville%20Mortgage-%205%20Ways%20to%20Invest%20in%20Real%20Estate.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>

Real estate investing is on the rise. Here are five different ways you can get involved.

</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Jan Leasure</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>

Real estate investing is on the rise. Here are five different ways you can get involved.

</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Libertyville, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>5 Remodeling Projects With the Best Return</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/5-remodeling-projects-with-best-return.html</link>
        
          <category>Home Seller Tips</category>
        
        <author>Jan Leasure</author>
        <pubDate>2017-08-24 11:55:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>http://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Jan%20Leasure/Libertyville%20Mortgage-%205%20Remodeling%20Projects%20With%20the%20Best%20Return.mp4</guid>
        <description>

Home remodeling is as hot as it’s ever been. Here are five projects that bring the best return on investment.

Home remodeling is hotter than ever.

According to researchers at Harvard University, remodeling investment is up 6% over last year and now makes up a $324 billion market.

According to a survey of remodelers and real estate professionals, there are five remodeling projects that offer the best returns:

1. Your kitchen. Kitchen remodeling can be as simple or as elaborate as you like. However, to maximize your return, keep your investment to under 20% of the value of your home—as is recommended by surveyed real estate professionals. The outcome? A whopping 85% return on your investment.

2. Your bathroom. A thorough bath remodeling project can cost up to $20,000. However, not only will it pay for itself, it should give you an added 80% return.

3. Your deck. Replacing your deck can cost you anywhere from a few thousand dollars to tens of thousands of dollars, depending on the size. The expected benefit will be similar to a bathroom remodeling project—around an 80% return for a fresh, new deck.

4. Your siding. Fading or worn-out siding can turn off potential buyers before they even step foot in your home. Replacing old siding will make it much easier to sell your home, and in addition, it should give you an 80% return on an investment of around $10,000.

5. Your windows. New windows can mean greater energy efficiency, increased thermal and acoustic comfort, and a more modern look. Homebuyers are well aware of this, and they are willing to pay accordingly. That’s why a typical window replacement should yield at least a 70% return on your investment.

“SOME WILL MAKE MORE SENSE FOR YOUR HOME THAN OTHERS.”

Clearly, some of them will make more sense for your home than others. If you’re considering selling your home, then just one of these projects could add tens of thousands of dollars to the price you’ll be able to get.

If you have any questions or want additional advice about which remodeling projects make sense for you, give me a call or send me an email. We can discuss all the details and I can give you an accurate estimate of what these projects could be worth. I look forward to hearing from you!
</description>
        <enclosure url="http://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Jan%20Leasure/Libertyville%20Mortgage-%205%20Remodeling%20Projects%20With%20the%20Best%20Return.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="http://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Jan%20Leasure/Libertyville%20Mortgage-%205%20Remodeling%20Projects%20With%20the%20Best%20Return.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>

Home remodeling is as hot as it’s ever been. Here are five projects that bring the best return on investment.

</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Jan Leasure</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>

Home remodeling is as hot as it’s ever been. Here are five projects that bring the best return on investment.

</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Libertyville, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>How the Feds Recent Rate Hike Impacts Our Market</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/how-feds-recent-rate-hike-impacts-our.html</link>
        
          <category>Libertyville Mortgages</category>
        
        <author>Jan Leasure</author>
        <pubDate>2017-07-31 13:30:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>http://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Jan%20Leasure/Libertyville%20Mortgage-%20How%20the%20Feds%20Recent%20Rate%20Hike%20Impacts%20Our%20Market.mp4</guid>
        <description>

The Fed’s recent rate hike shouldn’t have any significant impact on our market. In fact, it might actually stimulate it.

On June 14th, the Federal Reserve increased its federal funds interest rate by 0.25%. They’re also widely expected to raise rates once or twice more over the course of 2017. What does this mean for the real estate market?

While any action by the Fed always garners a lot of attention, I believe these increases will not have any significant impact on our market.

First of all, mortgage rates have actually trended lower in the wake of the Fed’s recent announcement. The 30-year mortgage rate recently hit 3.9%, the lowest level in 2017. In fact, it’s a common pattern for the mortgage rate and the Fed rate to move in opposite directions, and the same thing has happened the last two times the Fed raised rates.

Second, the economy continues to do well. The Fed decided to increase its rate because unemployment and inflation are low, household spending is picking up, and we’ve seen steady growth for the past nine years. This is good news for the real estate market. As expected, we continue to see strong demand and a corresponding increase in home prices.

“THESE INCREASES WILL NOT HAVE ANY SIGNIFICANT IMPACT ON OUR MARKET.”

Third, while the Fed’s rate increase is normally meant to cool off the economy, it might actually stimulate it in this case. Because interest rates were so low for such a long period of time, experts believe the recent increases might ease pressure on the financial system and encourage lending.

Case in point: since the Fed started raising its rate in December 2016, total mortgages are up 2.5% year over year.

In conclusion, while any move by the Fed is likely to lead to a lot of hand-wringing, I believe the real estate market will not be affected and will continue on its own healthy course. Nonetheless, it’s clear that right now is a uniquely good moment for everyone in the real estate market. Today’s low mortgage rates are good for homebuyers because they make homes more affordable.

If you have any questions about our market or you’re thinking of buying or selling a home, give me a call or send me an email. I’d love to help.
</description>
        <enclosure url="http://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Jan%20Leasure/Libertyville%20Mortgage-%20How%20the%20Feds%20Recent%20Rate%20Hike%20Impacts%20Our%20Market.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="http://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Jan%20Leasure/Libertyville%20Mortgage-%20How%20the%20Feds%20Recent%20Rate%20Hike%20Impacts%20Our%20Market.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>

The Fed’s recent rate hike shouldn’t have any significant impact on our market. In fact, it might actually stimulate it.

</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Jan Leasure</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>

The Fed’s recent rate hike shouldn’t have any significant impact on our market. In fact, it might actually stimulate it.

</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Libertyville, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>How Do Fannie Maes Recent Changes Affect Those With Student Debt?</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/how-do-fannie-maes-recent-changes.html</link>
        
          <category>Homebuyer Tips</category>
        
        <author>Jan Leasure</author>
        <pubDate>2017-06-19 12:41:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>http://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Jan%20Leasure/Libertyville%20Mortgage-%20How%20Do%20Fannie%20Maes%20Recent%20Changes%20Affect%20Those%20With%20Student%20Debt%253F.mp4</guid>
        <description>

Today I want to inform you about how Fannie Mae, the nation’s largest underwriter of mortgages, recently introduced three new rules that will affect those with student debt.

If you have a student loan or you are a cosigner on one, I have some good news for you.

Fannie Mae, the nation’s largest underwriter of mortgages, recently introduced three new rules that will affect those with student debt.

These new rules can make it easier to get a mortgage, and they can make it easier to pay off your (or your kids’) student loans.

The first change is for those on income-based repayment plans, where having a high debt-to-income ratio is the No. 1 reason for not being approved for a mortgage.

Fannie Mae previously used a very conservative 1% of the total loan instead of the actual monthly payment. This can drastically lower your debt-to-income ratio and give you a much better chance of qualifying for a mortgage.

Some folks are lucky enough to have their student debt paid by their parents or even by their employer. The thing is, Fannie Mae didn’t take this into account when calculating the debt-to-income ratio. That’s the second new change.

If your employer or your parents have been paying off your student debt and you can show evidence of this for the past 12 months, then this debt won’t be counted in your debt-to-income ratio. This makes it more likely you will qualify for a mortgage.

If you can qualify for a mortgage right now, you definitely should. Rates are still at a historical low, and lots of great houses have recently come on the Libertyville market.

Fannie Mae also makes it possible to refinance your mortgage for more than the value of your home. Normally, there is a 0.25% fee that applies to any cash you take out in this way.The third big change is that Fannie Mae will now waive that fee when you use this cash to pay off a student loan.

This applies whether the loan is yours, or you’re a cosigner. If the mortgage rate is significantly lower than the student loan rate, it can make sense to refinance in this way, and the new rule makes it cheaper to do so.

If you need help understanding these new guidelines to see whether they’re right for you, or you have questions about putting them into practice, get in touch with me. I’ll be glad to help.

I hope to hear from you soon!
</description>
        <enclosure url="http://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Jan%20Leasure/Libertyville%20Mortgage-%20How%20Do%20Fannie%20Maes%20Recent%20Changes%20Affect%20Those%20With%20Student%20Debt%253F.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="http://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Jan%20Leasure/Libertyville%20Mortgage-%20How%20Do%20Fannie%20Maes%20Recent%20Changes%20Affect%20Those%20With%20Student%20Debt%253F.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>

Today I want to inform you about how Fannie Mae, the nation’s largest underwriter of mortgages, recently introduced three new rules that will affect those with student debt.

</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Jan Leasure</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>

Today I want to inform you about how Fannie Mae, the nation’s largest underwriter of mortgages, recently introduced three new rules that will affect those with student debt.

</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Libertyville, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>You Dont Need a Down Payment</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/you-dont-need-down-payment.html</link>
        
          <category>Homebuyer Tips</category>
        
        <author>Jan Leasure</author>
        <pubDate>2017-05-22 15:45:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>http://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Jan%20Leasure/Libertyville%20Mortgage-%20You%20Dont%20Need%20a%20Down%20Payment.mp4</guid>
        <description>

Today, I want to share with you all the options you have for an affordable down payment as a homebuyer.

What’s the biggest obstacle to homeownership?

According to a recent survey, “saving enough for a down payment” comes at the top of the list. A whopping 55% of prospective homebuyers cited this as their main stumbling block.

And with the continuing growth of home prices, things aren’t getting any easier. In fact, homeownership rates reached a 20-year low last November.

It wasn’t always like this.

A decade ago, many lenders were offering easy, no-money-down mortgages.

However, after the financial crisis, mortgage standards have become more restrictive. A typical mortgage now requires a 20% down payment.

“55% CITED THE LACK OF A DOWN PAYMENT AS THEIR MAIN STUMBLING BLOCK.”

Here’s the good news.

If you have decent credit and a steady income, you might be qualified for a number of specialized programs that require no or very little down payment. Here are a few of the top options.

First, there’s the USDA loan, which is valid for homes in certain regions, such as rural and suburban areas.

With zero money down and lenient credit requirements, the USDA loan can be a great choice for many homeowners.

Second, there’s the VA loan, which you can apply for if you or your spouse served in a branch of the military.

It’s possibly the most generous zero-money-down mortgage because of low interest rates and low closing costs.

Third, there’s the FHA loan. It does require a 3.5% down payment — still drastically more achievable than the 20% required for a conventional mortgage.

Finally, there are a number credit unions and first-time homebuyer programs that might apply to your particular situation.

There’s one important thing you should know.

If you get one of these no-money-down mortgages, chances are good you will be required to pay private mortgage insurance, which can drive up your monthly payments.

Fortunately, private mortgage insurance will disappear after your mortgage balance is under 80%. Also, the money you do pay will be tax deductible in most cases.

In short, there are lots of options to make owning a home a reality for you, even if you haven’t saved up tens of thousands of dollars.

If you’re considering buying a home, give me a call and we can discuss your options.

Buying a Libertyville Home? Click here to complete your loan application.

And if you need more advice on getting a no-money-down loan, give us a call at (847) 362-1335.
</description>
        <enclosure url="http://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Jan%20Leasure/Libertyville%20Mortgage-%20You%20Dont%20Need%20a%20Down%20Payment.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="http://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Jan%20Leasure/Libertyville%20Mortgage-%20You%20Dont%20Need%20a%20Down%20Payment.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>

Today, I want to share with you all the options you have for an affordable down payment as a homebuyer.

</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Jan Leasure</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>

Today, I want to share with you all the options you have for an affordable down payment as a homebuyer.

</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Libertyville, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Tips to Replenish Your Self-Confidence</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/tips-to-replenish-your-self-confidence.html</link>
        
          <category>Life Lessons</category>
        
        <author>Jan Leasure</author>
        <pubDate>2017-03-20 13:33:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>http://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Jan%20Leasure/Libertyville%20Mortgage-%20Tips%20to%20Replenish%20Your%20Self-Confidence.mp4</guid>
        <description>

I recently read some advice for self-confidence from a teenage girl’s website, and I think it can actually be really helpful to you and your career. Try thinking about these scenarios in a different way to help yourself.

Sometimes when we use our same introduction or phrasing over and over again, we can get a little bit stale. In turn, I think we can also lose a little bit of self-confidence.

I came across this recent bit of advice from a teen girl’s website, actually. It’s something you can share with anyone to help with the idea of self-confidence: “What can I say to myself?”

Instead of “I’m not good at this,” try thinking “what am I missing?” Instead of “I’m awesome at this!” try thinking “I’m on the right track.” Instead of “I give up,” try thinking “I’ll use some of the strategies we’ve learned.”

Instead of thinking “This is too hard,” think, “This might take some time and effort.” Instead of, “I can’t make this better,” think, “I can always improve, so I’ll keep trying.” I think this is something I struggle with in my own office. Likewise, another one that was kind of personal and funny to me was, “I just can’t do math.” I never said I couldn’t do math, but I was never fond of algebra.

Instead of “I made a mistake,” think “Mistakes help me learn better.” Instead of “She’s so smart, I’ll never be that smart,” think “I’m going to figure out how she does it so I can try it (or so I can kick her ass!)”

Another one I really like is instead of thinking, “It’s good enough,” think “Is it really my best work?” I’ve had this situation transpire with me several times over the last year with people I’ve met through networking groups that I hired. I was disappointed in their work knowing that they didn’t do their best, and this is something that I started asking them. I’d say “I’m going to pay you for this, but is this really your best work?”

Finally, the last item was, “Plan A didn’t work,” when you should be thinking, “Good thing the alphabet has 25 more letters.”

Hopefully, this helps you in your networking and your education. If you have any questions for me or there’s anything I can do to help you in your career, give me a call or send me an email. I’d love to help you out!
</description>
        <enclosure url="http://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Jan%20Leasure/Libertyville%20Mortgage-%20Tips%20to%20Replenish%20Your%20Self-Confidence.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="http://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Jan%20Leasure/Libertyville%20Mortgage-%20Tips%20to%20Replenish%20Your%20Self-Confidence.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>

I recently read some advice for self-confidence from a teenage girl’s website, and I think it can actually be really helpful to you and your career. Try thinking about these scenarios in a different way to help yourself.

</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Jan Leasure</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>

I recently read some advice for self-confidence from a teenage girl’s website, and I think it can actually be really helpful to you and your career. Try thinking about these scenarios in a different way to help yourself.

</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Libertyville, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Woman of the House: Liz Cannon</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/woman-of-house-liz-cannon.html</link>
        
          <category>Libertyville Real Estate</category>
        
        <author>Jan Leasure</author>
        <pubDate>2017-02-03 15:47:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <guid>http://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Jan%20Leasure/Libertyville%20Mortgage-%20Feb%201.mp4</guid>
        <description>

Are you curious why so many people choose us to help them buy and sell homes? Let Liz Cannon tell you.

Here at Liberty Mortgage, we value our clients’ well-being above all else. As a testament to our dedication and the quality of service we provide, today we’ve brought in a former client of ours, Liz Cannon, to share her experience of working with us.

“I could not be happier with Jan and her team and their services, hard work, and dedication,” Liz says. “They seriously were a lifesaver during the home buying process and I highly recommend if you are a first-time home buyer or looking to refinance your home that she’s the first person you call.”

Liz met Jan during a guest lecture she gave about mortgages at the College of Lake County in 2014. She left such a favorable impression that Liz was the first person she contacted when she and her husband decided to buy a house last year. Jan remembered Liz from their encounter and immediately invited her and her husband into her office for a thorough consultation.

“She really does go the extra mile for her clients. She’s very charismatic. She used to be a teacher, so she’s great at explaining things in a way that isn’t confusing, and she doesn’t make you feel stupid for asking any sorts of questions. I highly recommend her and I’d never buy a house without her.”

It was our pleasure to be able to help Liz and her husband buy their first house. If you are thinking about buying a home, please don’t hesitate to contact us. It would be our pleasure to help you too.
</description>
        <enclosure url="http://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Jan%20Leasure/Libertyville%20Mortgage-%20Feb%201.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="http://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Jan%20Leasure/Libertyville%20Mortgage-%20Feb%201.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>

Are you curious why so many people choose us to help them buy and sell homes? Let Liz Cannon tell you.

</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Jan Leasure</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>

Are you curious why so many people choose us to help them buy and sell homes? Let Liz Cannon tell you.

</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Libertyville, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
    <copyright>Jan Leasure</copyright>
    <media:credit role="author">Jan Leasure</media:credit>
    <media:rating>nonadult</media:rating>
    <media:description type="plain">If you are looking to buy or sell a home, get all the information and the latest updates, tips, and tricks from Diamond Residential Mortgage - your professional Libertyville Real Estate Agents.</media:description>
  </channel>
</rss>
